Guide to the A.M. Rosenthal papers, 1959-2004
The New York Public Library. Manuscripts and Archives Division.
- Series VI: Subject files, 1987-2002; 379529; 15 boxes
  - Eulogies, 379596 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Evans-Novak, 379597 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Fallaci, Oriana, 379598 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Falun Gong, 379599 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Farber, Myron, 379600 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Farrakhan, Louis, 379601 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 379602 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Female genital mutilation, 379603 (Box 27, Folder 13-15)
  - First Amendment, 379604 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Foreign policy, 379605 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Foxman, Abraham, 379606 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Freedom House, 379607 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Gates, Henry Louis, 379608 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Gays, 379609 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Gelb party, 379610 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - GenerationA.com, 379611 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Germany, 379612 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Giuliani, Rudolph, 379613 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Gorbachev, Mikhail, 379614 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Greece, 379615 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Haiti, 379616 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Harvard University, 379617 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Hollywood movies, 379618 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Holocaust, 379619 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Horowitz, Michael, 379620 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Huffington, Arianna, 379621 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Human rights, 379622 (Box 28, Folder 19-20)
  - Hungary, 379623 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Hussein, Saddam, 379624 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Immigration, 379625 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - India, 379626 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - International Religious Freedom Act, 379627 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Iran, 379628 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Iraq, 379629 (Box 29, Folder 7-12)
  - Ireland, 379630 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Israel, 379631 (Box 29, Folder 14-15)
  - Israel, 379632 (Box 30, Folder 1-4)
  - Japan, 379633 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Jerusalem Post, 379634 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Jewish issues, 379635 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, 379636 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Journalism and The Times, 379637 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Kalahari, 379638 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Kashmir, 379639 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 379640 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Koch, Edward, 379641 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Lantos, Tom, 379642 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Lazer, Victor and Nora, 379643 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Lithuania, 379644 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Marion Prison, 379645 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Million Youth March, 379646 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Mintz, Morton, 379647 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Muslim states, 379648 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Muslims, 379649 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - National Families in Action, 379650 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - National security, 379651 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Nazi skinheads, 379652 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Nazi war crimes, 379653 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - New York, 379654 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - New York Observer, 379655 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - New York Public Library, 379656 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - New York Times, 379657
    - Jayson Blair, 379658 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Policy, 379659 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - North American Free Trade Association, 379660 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 379661 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Nuclear armament, 379662 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Obituary book, 379663 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Oman, 379664 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Pakistan, 379665 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Pan Am, 379666 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Pentagon Papers, 379667 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Pentagon Papers conference, 379668 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Perot, H. Ross, 379669 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Perry, Father Michael, 379670 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Poland, 379671 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Police, 379672 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Pollard, Jonathan, 379673 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Prague, 379674 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Presidential Medal of Freedom, 379675 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Press, 379676 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Proliferation, 379677 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Puerto Rico, 379678 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Pulitzer Prize, 379679 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Qaddafi, Muammar, 379680 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Radio Free Europe, 379681 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 379682 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Religion, 379683 (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
  - Religious persecution, 379684 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Rosenthal, Harold, 379685 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Savings and loan, 379686 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Schumer, Charles, 379687 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 379688 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Serbia/Croatia, 379689 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Severo, Richard, 379690 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Shalem Center, 379691 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Shea, Nina, 379692 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Shultz, George, 379693 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Sleeping sickness, 379694 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Sliwa, Maria, 379695 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - South Africa, 379696 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Soviet prisoners, 379697 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Union, 379698
    - Kazachkov, 379699 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - KGB, 379700 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Post-coup, 379701 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Sudan, 379702 (Box 34, Folder 3-6)
  - Syria, 379703 (Box 34, Folder 7-8)
  - Taiwan, 379704 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Talese, Gay, 379705 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Talese, Pamela (Century), 379706 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Terrorism, 379707 (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
  - Thirty-Eight Witnesses, 379708 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Tibet, 379709 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Turkey, 379710 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - United Nations, 379711 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - United States Commission on International Religious Freedom, 379712 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 379713 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Vietnam, 379714 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Wallace, Mike, 379715 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Wallenberg, Raoul, 379716 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Washington Times, 379717 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Wharton, Cliff, 379718 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Wiesel, Elie, 379719 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Wu, Harry, 379720 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Yugoslavia, 379721 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Series VII: Writings, 1961-2000; 379722; 4 boxes
  - General, 379723
    - Column Lists, 1987-2000; 379724 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      Arranged by subject and by date
    - Final New York Times column with signatures, 1999; 379725 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Moscow, n.d.; 379726 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Philippines, n.d.; 379727 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Reader's Digest (China), 1997; 379728 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Sophisticated Traveler introduction, 1984; 379729 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Story idea notebook, n.d.; 379730 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Wills, 1980, 1985; 379731 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Memoir, 379732
    - Prologue; Chapters 1-8, 379733 (Box 38, Folder 1-8)
    - 1961 manuscript, 379734 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - China (original transcripts), 379735 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - New York, 379736 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Outlines, 1991-1992; 379737 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Book notes--Office copy, 379738 (Box 39, Volume 1)
    - Family, U.N., India, Nehru, 379739 (Box 40, Volume 1)
    - Vietnam, India, Nepal, Poland, 379740 (Box 40, Volume 2)